qkport.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy

Qkport is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable web experience possible. You should be able to use our services without giving us any specific information about yourself. When we do need your personal information to provide additional and/or optional services that you request, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information. Qkport firmly respects your right to personal privacy, and we will collect and use information through our web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. 

**Part I: General Overview on Information Collection**

For the most part, you will not need to provide any private, personally identifiable information to use Qkport. 

In the course of normal operation Qkport, like many other popular sites, collect and process a large number of not personally identifiable, information such as IP addresses, browser type, browser language, and the date and time of your visits. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. This information is used primarily to operate our service, and at times, to monitor, develop and improve our services further. 

We do track and catalog the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is usually not associated with individual users. We use this tracking information to determine and continuously refine the accuracy and relevance of our services as well as to analyze which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

**Customer and Visitor Inquiries and Emails**

Qkport treats any information received through inquiries regarding our products, services or any other matter is treated as confidential and they are strictly used to analyze, understand and act upon it and where appropriate to prepare and send a reply. Under no circumstances Qkport discloses this information to any other party with out a genuine and justifiable reason or required to do so by law. 

**Use of Cookies**

Qkport may set and whenever necessary access its cookies in your computer. Qkport may also allow certain third-party, partner sites and advertisers to set cookies as part of the service and analyze traffic and usage patterns to help serve relevant advertisements and similar promotional services. Use of cookies by a third-party service is subject to the privacy policy of the third-party service provider. Qkport uses its own cookies as the basis for a number of personalized and customized features only and **by no means** used to track or determine their browising habits. 

**Use of Beacons**

Qkport may use beacons on our web site to analyze our traffic pattern, usefulness and popularity of certain parts of the site. Qkport may also use beacons in promotional email messages to determine whether the message was opened and acted on. We may use this information on email response to develop future promotions you may enjoy. 

**Advertisements**

Qkport depends on revenue accrued from online advertisements. It may allow third party agencies to run and manage advertisements in various sections of its sites. These third-party agencies may have their own policy regarding user data and personal information. Some advertisement agencies may use visitation information to help serve interest based or targeted advertisements. 

**Part II: Information Security**

Qkport always makes its best efforts to protect any user information with appropriate measures in order to prevent unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. User information may be used in a strictly limited manner in order to operate, improve or develop our products or services. 

**Part III: Third Party Sites**

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note that third party sites may have privacy standards that differ from ours. We do not control the content on any third party site, and we encourage you to read the privacy policies on third party sites when you click on their links. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer and/or collect personally identifiable information. 

**Part IV: Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Qkport may change or modify its privacy policy from time to time. Any changes or updates to our privacy policy will be posted in this site. 

v.1.6
